The ghosts are moving tonight
risk. Only. Manage this myself.
I'm want to put it. In just
a minute I'll show you the only really
haunted house and. Since it was build
a century ago seven people including my
brother up and murdered him. Since then
I've owned the house. Only spent one night
there and when they found me in the
morning. I was almost dead.
I'm critical aren't. And I've rented the
house voted it tonight so that my wife can
get. On to oust. C.
So I'm using. Every food and drink
and ghosts and perhaps even if you
met
a. Girl in private if any of you will spend
the next two hours in this house I'll
give you each ten thousand dollars. Or
your next of kin in case you go survive.
But you come out I think. It was my wife's
idea to have rockets coming
funeral cars. She so amusing. Her
sense of humor is shall we say original I
dreamed up the terrorists it's empty now
but after
a night in the House of him who
now. This is brand Schroeder
a test pattern so no doubt
a brave man but don't you think you can
be much braver if you're paid for and I
happen to know that Lance needs the ten
thousand are given if he's brave enough to
stay all night this is Ruth bridges
you've no doubt read her column in the
newspapers she says a reason for
coming to the party is to write
a feature article on ghosts. She's
also desperate for money Campbell.
You've already met Watson Pritchett
a man living in mortal fear of her house
and yet he is risking his life to spend
another night here and wonder
why. He says for money.
This is Dr David trying to psych actress
he claims that my ghost will help is work
on hysteria. Or don't you see
a little chip green there
around the mouth and I.
This is Nora Manning I picked her from
the thousands of people who work for me
because she needed the ten thousand more
than most supports her oath. Isn't she
pretty. Funny starting now.
And you have until midnight
to find the house wanted.
Wow Where is everybody you know very warm
welcome it only the ghosts in this house
are glad we're here we all strangers
to each other don't get to
know each other I'm friend I
don't even know may I know I met
a lad Schroeder is Frederick Law In
a friend of yours I've heard of him but
I've never met him I worked for one of his
companies but I've never seen him
I never met the man either just
a phone call to know him. But then
you're the only one of us who does I
don't know all the details about running
the house were done by mail he's quite
wealthy isn't he millions and five wives
I believe far I think so by fifty
thousand dollars body for only five
people is a little steep even for
a millionaire. Going to
hot anybody this would
certainly be the house I'd do it. To
close the door.
As things measures are still.
At about. Our guest here and fortunately
still alive your face on yes.
Yes we did have Bill and
a lot of fairly strict rules and you had
to play and clean atmosphere go out and
you know have ghosts are
the never Tasveer. That's
a very fetching outfit
but hardly suitable for
a party I'm not going to. Spend the night
goes party was your idea remember since
it's going to cost me fifty thousand dollars
I want you to have fun the party was
mad into you in ninety dollars games.
While the strange and out of our friends
friends do we have any friends who
know your jealousy too can. I had
a reason for inviting each
guest I wanted kind of
a cross-section from psychiatry's to
typist and from drunks to jet pilot
they share one thing they all need money.
Let's see if they're brave enough today
and you call this
a pretty good day. Why
do you always do that it spoils the
champagne you might explode and never does
but you guarantee that that
isn't funny Frederick make
a good headline Playboy kills wife
with champagne cork. Are you joining
me thank you. Just
a sip right approach your humor my humor
is fine day and I haven't put it and.
It's always good to know that. I have
something you'll enjoy
the party more go on.
Your chest just so tacky and I'm not going
to party. With all my wives or at least
a career will not still
alive. Would you go away for
a million dollars tax free. You want
a dog and I did give the dog.
Jealousy isn't tax free you
possessiveness is maddening. Ever
a man had grounds for divorce but can't
prove him this time will come. You'll slip
up one of these days thanks up for
a long enough to remember the fun
we had when you poisoned me.
Something you ate the duct tape yes I
asked Nick on the rocks. And about.
You do it again if you thought you could
get away with it would Johnny what makes
you think that. Something about.
Here that hanging is very uncomfortable OK
should get any more ideas. Don't let the
ghosts in the goobers disturb you.
They only go in the house you
don't sit up all night thinking of ways
to get rid of me it makes wrinkles.
This is what used to my brother and her
sister to pieces we found parts of the
bodies all over the house and places you
wouldn't think the funny thing is the
heads have never been found hands and feet
and things like that but no heads. The
wife probably in a rage
threatened her husband with
a knife and then carried
away by his Spirit took
a swing at him and then we went on from
there but this is certainly what I am going
to people that she killed Mr Pritchard
only to her husband and her sister no one
else was here so there are two loose heads
just floating around in his own way you
can he has them at night they whisper to
each other and then cry. But since our
host isn't here would
anyone care to make me
a drink said to me what would you have.
Good evening. I'm your host
Frederick Florida where all
strangers to each other
let's get acquainted with
a drink surely Mr lawn. I advise you to
call this party off now the ghosts are
already moving on that's
a bad sign let me apologize for my rights
you enjoy the flavor. And doctors have
the same. Now before the party begins
let's go over the details. That
caretakers will leave it midnight locking
it in here until they come back in the
morning. Once the door is locked there's
no way out the windows have the
jail would be proud and the only
door to the outside locks like
a vote there's no electricity
no phone no one within miles.
No way to call for help. Like
a coffin. So if any of you decide
not to stay for the party's
image let me know before midnight of course
if you leave or I shan't be able to pay
you anything I'm interested in
your reasons for this. Party aside
from pleasant company goes Dr I
think everyone wonders what they
would do if they saw him go and now my
wife is giving us all the opportunity to
find. Him using goes to being only
creations of hysteria your party
should be
a success Prichard here promise
this is genuine go seven now maybe
more before morning that's two for four
men have been murdered in this house
and three when you bend your body very
well Mr alarm four of us I'm in three A
WOMEN. Goes for everybody.
Richard why don't you take us on
a tour through the house and
see what happens can you.
See that stain. Blood. A
young girl was killed here.
And whatever got her wasn't
human toll stand there where.
It's too late they've marked you ridiculous
through probably that must be but it is
with follow me I would say any self
respecting male ghost I hope it doesn't come
back just a frigid Joe the life of the
party hasn't even started yet wasn't there
a man who threw his wife into
a wine batter something that
was in the cellar there's been
a murder almost every place in this house.
All it along to
a Mr Norton. Who did I hear
she was electrocuted late. Mr
nor will it be
a family why. Place Why do you think
it was any good at. All he felt
that the Bassett through or in.
She was supposed to stay down.
But the bones came up. It's
a funny thing. That none of the murders
here were just ordinary. Just shooting
a stabbing. They've all
been sort of wild violent.
The. God she didn't fall in
you mean you're still out
there.
You.
Destroy everything with
parents life. Just leaves
a bone. Fires
dry and dusty down here.
There's. A cure for that stick
too much.
How do you get invited to
this party. And I'm gone I
mean what do you do you. Just
a line fed everybody you get ten thousand
dollars but I didn't say anything about
being locked in you know. You just made
it with me on the fall but neither have I
and I just say I'm going to stay if I
don't I lose ten thousand dollars.
I'm going to stay to ten
thousand dollars. If you
believe in ghosts. You know. Well I
agree with that doc says you can spoke
yourself why do you think you are
really there for one of them.
What do you do with it and if we get it
what do you mean if we get forty payoff if
we stay. Ten thousand and
no more and when I make
a list. We're going and I will be elected
now I'm the only one in the family who
can make any money. Or I've
never seen so many doors.
Closet.
Bottles.
Does it go anywhere.
They.
Like Lance is gone and at the
cost of living I mean. This is
a lesson Kong on fire.
You are right. IN THE MONEY.
Must just above my head.
The only way to come to it is. To run
it on the wall. You didn't do that to
just. Let's get
a bad. I just. I
wonder why they didn't
kill him. He didn't.
They.
Bring you came in you said something about
a ghost there was something what did it
look like how do you think it was wearing
a black thing that went all the
way to the throne which you were
a little frightened at the
time. Quite yet. That this. Is
hysteria going Dr how do you explain what
happened to Max first that hysteria to.
Really get that checked
in the dead Thanks Mark.
What for me and all. The
ghosts are coming closer Mr lawn do you
really believe in your pay go stunt your
preaching for the Knights over
you will too but you like
a drink plant No thanks I
like what you got I am.
Really going to pay any when you stayed
all night certainly ten thousand dollars
will be much red tape delayed. You
know Hurry dear I'm frankly yes. I
frantically.
Someone or something was in it
when I came in where the door
was locked out of the get out
what you saw might have been
a ghost nor ever what was in it with me was
no ghost I don't know I was so scared.
Oh so different do you have.
Three seconds I was out. Twelve feet.
Three seconds. And I knock on the other
wall with you have you knock on this wall.
Oh.
What
a comfort I mean here. One
of the grand out of your arse
Lassie doesn't run it just
a lot Yeah why didn't I
see. You don't believe me.
OK.
ANABEL. You must be Miss Manning.
I realize this is
a very unusual and very very dull
but I wouldn't like to freshen up.
This is your own. Depressing isn't
it. I gather been matched I'm
going to read. Perfect atmosphere
for my husband's party.
Manager come in. He said he'd give me
ten thousand dollars. But if you don't
know my supervisor just
came and said I'd invite.
A long illness but I just never knowing.
Why you. What we're doing wandering
around by yourself. While I was in the
cellar woodlands Mr Shelley and I
just left that song. Don't do it again.
Don't go anywhere in this house by.
The picture of a snow and ice for
a live human but you are
in danger. We all own. Who
. I hope your stake you never.
Anabel only
a can do them think but not exactly how
you talk to no no I'm not sure of the
planet you purchased Oh it's just
a bump on the head.
Which is my room I have
a fifty Thank you Mrs lark. And if.
You were with the young girl in the cellar
level she saw. More shit and you don't
look like the type go round up anything
that really happened. Nora thought she saw
a ghost but I didn't see anything she was
just frightened and mad at me I think I
killed her about. I wouldn't joke about
anything else that happened to. I don't
tell me you're taking all this seriously
I too. Would like to find out what could
me know. And he'd have me back on
you. Sure I guess oh. Look what's going on
here anyway I mean what is with this party
this is no party he's planning something
your husband had lighted one. Must be
pretty big he's going to lay out fifty
thousand money doesn't
mean anything. He has
a reason for getting your solo paid to
this good fellow. Who work for you doesn't
even know I was going to get you back and
why you're here. What can you go through
with oh he thinks
a big money like is going to get away with
anything you know of course that I'm his
fourth wife. The first simply
disappeared get into attack.
I don't want to join. You mean he
had all his doctors had died of
heart attacks. Two girls. In the
twenty's. We were going to do
I was going to sometimes
insane nothing matters to.
Her too he would kill me if he could.
And I bet you're missing all the fun.
Nora Manning was I was killed by
a falling chandelier I had
bashed his head in even
a saturnine sack I just bandaged him.
And you want to go in consoling you do
most men in your action. Is so
clever Frederick so I lie awake
nights wondering my marriage was rather
a mistake he didn't marry me dear and
he chews on lies in that no mistake.
Area very big with the last time I'm not
going to YOUR MONEY. For the last time
it's not my party but yours.
And you are going. And.
Already you know. Are you ready dear yet.
To adore me as much as. I
do want to be with you.
It's almost time to lock up the house
and then your party really begin. To
wonder how to manage.
It's close to midnight
tonight. OK to be down to.
Go into your house maybe. It's almost
midnight you know we're all going to get
together down in the living
room I used to like I do I get.
You. You.
Come with us come with
us before he kills you.
Weren't Nora this matter.
Don't they you know what happened.
That's Jonas lads and his wife. They've
been caretakers here for years she's been
my. Good day here.
Documents likely ever be a case of
hysteria and I think you're just
a little upset not just in.
Getting. The Magic.
This is my wife these are our guests this
bridge is after Trent you know what's
going Pritchard of course Manning
and this is land Schroeder.
What about the ten Q.
He wants to kill who wants
to kill. To. Marry have your
attention please I think you all remember
the bark and we made about staying all
night ten thousand dollars apiece if any
of you don't survive fifty thousand
dollars will be divided amongst
the rest of you if I should die
you will be paid by my state when the
door is locked from the outside by the
caretakers will all be forced to stay in
this house until morning if any of you
decide not to stay you must be with
the caretakers now you won't have
a chance to change your minds later because
there'll be no way to get out. I don't
want to date wait.
To see midnight here who told them they
could leave and never leave before midnight
and they've gone now. I was going to ask
you whether you wanted to stay or not but
it seems that the caretakers have made the
decision for you we're all home locked
in now I don't want to stay and I'm sorry
my dear but it's too late now that I
haven't you had enough of this silly game
getting caught if it is people and let
them go home that paid in
face. This is your passion
remember. In spite of my wife's faith
in my ability to do the impossible
we will all have to stay in this house
until eight o'clock in the morning but we
have some party favors for
you in these little coffins.
My wife's idea. I must say I think it's
rather dangerous I suppose you all know how
to use one of these things but in case you
don't you just press down on this lever
with your and then pull the trigger. You
see they're loaded. These are no good
against the dead only the living.
Parents. Or.
Are taking. This bridge yours.
And yours yours dear and you need it because
your idea who knows you may want to
use it on me before this marriage
of. All these guns away there won't
be any good I agree with Richard on that
board although not to the same reason Doc
dread. Going to approve of
a little party. Suppose Nora had had
a gun when she mistook the blind woman for
I don't think anyone else is going to
walk around in total darkness. Oh I'm sure
we're not going to go running around the
house shooting each other on June the nurse
here makes people do amazing things.
To Bitch. You said your
sister not killed a man and
a woman here and cut them up. You said
they found hands and feet but they never
found any heads. Would you like to see one
of those hands when you are like if they
want to know they are well just beyond.
That ng. I really don't mean to.
Just go look in my thinking just told.
You within here how one fat Nora I think
your little upset would you characterise
it if out. How.
You can tell right to leave a
virus on top. I wish you'd taken
a sedative so what do you suppose she
thought you so they're closing in on
a book that I think somebody
will stay with you could be
a million people around her if
they want to hear that. But if
she's right he's too drunk to know what
he's talking about I wonder. Joining him
and I.
Do think it would do any good if you went
in and talked and you think there really
was a head in your suitcase. Like
a puppy right over the edge but would you
sort of stay up here I mean in case she
needs. Oh I. Just called.
Are you sure there are only seven people
in this massive except for the ghosts I
don't believe those nor in frightening
women nor is cases gunfire in the.
Apps to where you suggest we do about
it or don't frighten her any more.
LAURA
Laura. Laura
.
What do you know about this taken or in
a little while should be
one of them. Where your.
Parish it's too late it's too late you'll
never find her again Richard if you know
where she is but
a tell me now gone she's gone with
them nothing you can do about. Nora
. She's dead Mr.
You know what hang to so serious.
I mean they think it's an ash.
Get you to kill me. Get you to pee and
poop in that room. And then you will
know when they had me. In
thought I was dead who.
Mistook laws. Are you sure
about this. To go with it
was dark but it must be me it. Is
anybody seen you since you left.
It to people in that room that
I went by and. Smartest that.
Are said she committed suicide
but I think somebody killed him.
I'm sure you've come to the same conclusion
I have yeah I think so let's all have
a meeting to discuss what
to do. Living room OK in
a minute. I
go downstairs now you lock yourself in
handle that anybody know you're here he
thinks you're dead he won't come here and
I'll get back as soon as I can you'll be
. If you have to.
You'll use it.
So greedy. So.
What are you doing in here we don't we what
do you mean coming in here. Let me take
you away drink they will if you don't want
your drug right out of the project why
did you come into this room and you only
want to understand I just dance one of.
Your white isn't there anymore. She's
already joined them Bridget I've had enough
of your spook talk get our juice something
don't come back into this room again.
Whereas what's your name Nora I didn't
disturb us and I don't think those
concerns are your own I missed
a lot. Isn't there some way we can get
out of this house now. Not at all
we could try breaking out the only door on
the outside is made of steel the bars of
the windows are set in solid
stone we've got to stay.
I'm not afraid of your ghosts
Pritchett but I am afraid
when we came here a few hours ago
the only thing we had in common was
a ten thousand dollars we get now however
we share something else the death of this
is lucky so far tonight one
of us was almost killed by
a falling chandelier one of us was
mysteriously slugged one of us has been driven
to the brink of absolute hysteria.
And one of us is dead with
these accidents suicide we missed a have
a six more hours six hour six of us.
I'm going to. Be Next how
it happened let me ask you
a question Dr you were the first one to see
my wife there did you also see anything
that she could have climbed up on
and then jumped No Did any of.
Their West know how then did she get
up there so high exactly Mr Lauren
how she couldn't have pulled
a self but there she couldn't have dropped
from the ceiling do you think your wife
killed herself you know she
was murdered by one of
you or you missed another
and to deliberately kill
someone you must have
a reason we were all strangers
to your wife only you had
a motive for murder or has been hasn't it
some guy wanted to kill his wife. But has
been hasn't had a thousand
opportunities to do it in such
a way so that he'd never
be suspected I'm not such
a food as to hang my
wife from the ceiling by
a rope the fact remains that you are
one of us noted Mrs Laura and that's
a matter for the police so how do we get
the police that's my point we can't until
morning what began as
a silly party given by an eccentric
does not involve us all in met at once
Pritchard may be right if another motors
in the works let's stop now and not them
that there. May be one of us saw too much
why should even
a millionaire want to give each of us ten
thousand dollars to spend one night in
a gloomy old house to see them ghosts have
a party know if you can try me Dr and there's
the very big guilty of murder Ah this
is him getting us anywhere somebody killed
Mrs Laura and we know that one of us is
guilty and the rest of us are innocent OK
I would we have to do for the next six
hours protect us from each other.
Everything I don't think anything I
just know that I'm going to my room and
if anybody comes in I'll shoot him or her
and if we all stay in our rooms will be
safe because the innocent will have no
reason to leave his room and the guilty
will admit his guilt if he or she does and
we all have guns we're all
agreed. I wish this night.
It's. I tell you because to make
any difference. Through is shit.
Let's see this is saying good night.
Good night.
Good night for.
Room.
Are the lights.
OK. They've all got their rooms and like
yourself this man from thinking it was so
dark down there maybe it was enough to
believe it was them all right he tried
because you hate to kill his wife. How
can you be sure she tried to warn me
ask with the help of. The doc thinks he's
going to try and kill one of us. Another
must be
a way out of this place and I'm going to
find it and get the police before he does
I'm going with. If he finds out you're
alive. No no you're safer here than anyplace
else I just lock yourself
in and keep quiet.
If I find a way out
a come back and get you. The
power.
The.
Weak. Here.
Aid.
So.
The other.
Mission if. Certainly not is either somebody
else in this house one of the Slept is
room did you hear anything. Organ
music that someone walking to catch or.
You look downstairs look up here right
after maybe only minutes seconds left to
someone's life why waste time.
It's almost over doubting.
Every detail respecting.
That's happening. We've done
it perfect crime beautiful.
Has she killed him Not yet but she will.
Get me out of this
hanging Highness. Taking
a girl so low my time is it but first I
couldn't get Norah to want to protect
itself with
a gun after you appeared at the window
everything began to work just as we planned
you felt wonderful just to touch the funny
drover in the completest still. Believe
with all that planning. There's no know
what's happening on the way to the cellar
so schedule should the first thing move.
And Frederick on his way to the cellar to
. David are you sure none of them will
suspect what an hysterical gun accidentally
shoots somebody who would suspect that we
planned it that way that we drove into it
but about my SO SAD but just a
ghost party gag we claim it was
a dummy since I'm the only one it touched
and you can't take. But they had no idea
what they were really doing what about
Nora she's not stupid you know darling
Believe me everything we planned is working
perfectly Nora's sure Fredrik marriage
you she thinks predicate actor in the
Senate not me now nor is almost out of
a mind with fear heads the music your hanging
I tell you when pretty close initial
shooting. Taking to. David
you want to be the head.
When you hear the shot come down said.
Way. Way.
Out.
They.
Hate.
Us.
So.
Me.
Everything that. I. Used
to come with me better this would be.
Me.
That and
a better. Crime you two plan was
indeed Paris. Only the victim this
would not have been the
murders you know. It's
a pity you didn't know when you started
your game up from that day that I was
praying to.
You must be why you can't hear Oh
it's right all of you hear someone.
I shot me too low and he's down in
the wind that. I don't think fell.
Hit him he don't lock.
You didn't shoot anyone my dear I loaded
your gun with blanks I can tell you
are now trying to my wife are
planning to kill me they say oh
Trent tried to throw me in the fact
my wife stumbled and found I'm ready
for justice to decide if
I'm innocent or guilty.
Now there now. Have been more money.
Coming from meaner. Than this country you.